Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
I deserve it. What day is it?
Hold on. What day is it? Is it Sunday?
Happy Sunday, everybody. Good to see you.
But I guess this narrative I've already been...
Oh my gosh, I was saying I was going to do bad things to myself.
Well, I was talking about trolling the trolls and...
Well, my chat was telling me, but I do want to remind people in case people forgot
because I'm sure I knew who's spreading this narrative.
It's his mod or Stephen King's mod, Christine.
Um, Christine, who was it that told me to go jump off a bridge, um, met at least 20
times, do it.
You should do it.
Oh, I know you said over the harness and stuff like that.
But actually, you know, it's not even like illegal to take your own life.
It is illegal to tell somebody to.
you know what she seems to do and says and you know she's especially you know
it's really sickening that it's a nurse this is somebody I mean a nurse
that's that's saying this also I have them I have on tape they thought I was
deleted I have on tape for encouraging
violence against me saying hey oh no jury would convict you
um
You know, they'll see they'll hear that, you know, he's weirdness and a weird stalker and no one will convict you and
Oh, there's you know, what there's not even gonna be karma if you did that, you know
AM
Not even karma, but you know what? I think that little happy
That little happy
Relationship is over. I think because we'll guess who's turned on beat it now
Okay, you don't have to guess.
I mean, it's like, it's just obvious.
Let's fucking go.
What's up, William?
How are you?
It's not fish taco.
I'm going to Starbucks to have a,
I have a S'mores Frappuccino waiting for me over there.
I want to shout out to the Donator
who hooked me up with the Starbucks.
Appreciate you so much.
And, you know, hey, what's up, William?
Yeah.
I mean, every now and then I knew,
I like McDonald's coffee, but you know.
Can't really be the store books for a bunch of the best things in the world, right?
So anyway, I don't know. It's just like, I mean it's like people
Get away with saying all this crazy shit to me if I troll back a little bit. Oh, you know
And it's like yeah, I don't know that woman was that woman's name. I don't know
I don't know if she's slow or whatever. I don't even know or I've never spoken to her before and she's like
Oh, well, you just went and she and you're trying. I mean, it's just some narratives
I can just hear other people putting in these people's heads
So it's kind of annoying. I mean ask me about it
I mean just like I even explain it and then they don't get it
I don't know. Is it just like I can't explain things right because it's like everybody else seems to get away with all this shit
And if I ever
Play back a little bit. I'm like
You know, it's a shocking bill and as usual, I don't know
We're talking about scapegoating. Oh
Yeah, the Elvis people claiming scapegoating a
Samman beat
Look at their own behavior, man. It's just crazy. But yeah, the honeymoon is over with beta and
AM apparently AM
which is probably referring to her from now on.
I'm not gonna be saying her name.
Makes me sick to even think about her.
This woman is saying, first of all,
that I sacrificed my baby, my black cat,
sacrificed in a cult ritual.
I don't have to, I mean, it's kind of meta,
but I have to keep explaining.
Calling, using the term cult makes it not a cult.
I mean,
No, no cult would call itself a cult. I mean, are people just retarded or are they just retarded? Yeah
They must be but yeah, she says on my sacrifice my cat Lenore
in order to gain some kind of power or something like that in my cult ritual and
Actually put a pole up about it. And then another pole is another pole. No. Yeah, I guess I guess she was just musing that
I am
Planning on
I'm breeding Lola.
So she has baby.
Yep, I'm getting Starbucks.
Thank you so much.
I, yeah, I'm getting, yeah, she's, oh my God.
Yeah, here we go.
Uh-oh, there we go.
I'm getting a S'mores Frappuccino to be ready for me to go.
But anyway, yeah, so she and Bita are now over
because I guess, you know, she says Bita is
Plotting with me to like sue her or something. I mean it just gets so stupid. I can't even like
imagine anymore
But yeah, she's like she said I was I'm breeding Lola
To sacrifice the kittens or something like that for magical power. Hey, bitch. Okay. Let me just play makes things clear
First of all, I wouldn't do any
stupid bizarre
Dumb shit like that. First of all, I would hope you had you know more sense than the mill
I don't know if anyone would do that kind of shit, but AM that's just a stupid theory and
Not true and against any part of my heart or anything if you actually knew me what you don't
obviously
But Lola's fucking spade
There won't be Lola won't be having any more kittens
She had one litter and as for my little pet cemetery, which I
Really mentioned that I have another cat named Remy who a few years ago
She had two letters of kittens, and the first litter,
one kitten passed away.
And the second litter, one was born, passed away,
and one ended up passing away, okay?
Just hard enough.
I mean, I share, I just close.
But you're saying I have like a little, like,
a little pet cemetery of like voodoo or something?
You're just a dumbass bitch. I'm sick of you.
Leave me alone and leave my pet's names out of your mouth.
You said leave me, you said to not contact you
or talk about you.
Look at you, you're doing polls about me killing my cats.
Again, you're a dumb ass bitch.
You're sick.
I thought, I don't know.
I thought you were like an intelligent person at one time.
You're not, you just don't,
I guess you know, you copied how people talk.
You know, you watched Oprah or something like that, copied how she talked and got, you know,
you're kind of well-spoken. You're just a dumbass. And from head to toe, probably the dumbest person
that ever, good morning. I love you, sweetie. I think, yeah, AM, you're one of the dumbest,
probably people in the world. These are the word I was coming to you.
And you're calling all this violence onto yourself
from through, you know, your Sandman and other.
Oh, I'm just a 50 year old innocent woman
that would never fly.
You threaten people all the time.
You're fucking doxing people.
I mean, everything you accuse people of doing, you do.
And I'm not even wanting to talk about it
because you're just like, I mean, I can't,
I can't go into this dumb level of thinking
that tries to figure out
what how your mind works or something.
Uh-oh, Hebs and Maya did.
Yeah, and but I'm getting blamed for this stuff for beta. Oh, I I
Docs me to beat it in and dox me even though be the set my home address and my telephone number to Eldo and then she said well
Oh, well, you know that he already doxed himself because you know somebody here with both. No, no, no, no
No, no, no, no. Well, I can say you doxxed yourself because your picture was out of your ex-fiance it
But posting your ex-fiance your stupid ex-fiance say he looks like a fucking big dork
Okay, posting his stupid photo on a thumbnail, which I took down right away
Remember you copyright struck me because it was on tripkicks video. Remember that I took it down right away
And you know, I didn't I didn't put on eight times. You'd have to ask me eight times
I did it instantly for you. I had this all on tape. I mean, it's like I was I think I had this codex
That I can just like fucking pull all this out really quickly because
You people are just liars. Most of the people are just fucking full of shit. There's liars. I tell the truth
I'm on camera. I'm right here. I'm right here. You can see everything
Stop talking about my cats. Stop making a fucking lies about me
I mean everything's such a lie and then there's stupid people like this
I don't know who this grace, you know this person graces
I mean she sounds like she she sounds like she has Downston or something like that
But she's over on money for 20s is speculating about me to be praise. I mean really
Stay in your lane, bitch
Okay, I mean I don't know
Hey, it's about to get more stupid or because some of these people are involved. I've never I've never knew I would encounter such retarded people in my entire
existence
But hey, thanks for making me feel like a fucking genius. I used to think I was dumb now
I feel like I'm fucking Albert Einstein compared to you you imbeciles and
That I'm not talking to any of the channels. They're listening and they know who they are
Maybe they don't
They are slow
jeez
Anyway, I got it
Um, this one has a couple shots of, uh,
a couple shots of a wrestle on top of it, too.
It's kind of good for a frappe, okay?
So, I'm home.
I'm gonna switch to my computer in a second.
Just give me one minute.
Sorry, I know a little bit.
I just woke up.
Hi, Sipha.
Hey, Noble.
Hey, guys.
How are you doing?
Hi.
Hey, grateful here. I'll put my link up. Oh my gosh. I need my background's a little bit. Is my camera down or something here?
Okay
What's up, dude? How are you?
Sip a how are you? Oh good to see you. It's been a while the coffee is good. Yeah
It's a it's a s'mores frappuccino has a graham cracker has marshmallow
marshmallow whip has a couple shots of espresso and probably a
S'mores flavored thing, but there you go. Let's see. Where you go? Where is it? There you go. Oh
I need to take my background down.
Good to see everybody.
Good morning, guys.
What is it?
Sunday morning, we'll go to the church of psyche.
There we go, there we go.
Uh-oh, yeah.
And so last night, I mean, I went to money for 20s,
kind of like got accosted there by, you know,
this one Grace and stuff, and I left.
And then I went,
To another show I think was money for 20s again. I'm not a hundred percent sure summer was there
I got to say hi to summer. You know that was cool
But Alex McQueen was there and he doesn't shut up and I was trying to I think I had 10 seconds to speak 10 seconds
I said just like just 10 seconds. Let me get let me get a word out
And they wouldn't let me I mean it's like I don't think it was like you know intentionally not trying to there
Just like you know Alex Alexander McQueen has a kind of a big mouth and stuff like that. Yeah, they're good
They saw them. They're hate bonding crystal turn on him. So he's
Wow, no, he's hate bonding with crystal now
well, and then AM
Really she really must be in love with him because you know, she the whole reason she said she got mad at me is because she said
I set her up because he was such a weirdo
Then why are you friends with them now now? She's promoting his show now
She's you know giving him secret little cheat codes that had beat you know, I and X or myself, which you know
Good luck. Okay. I can play video games, too. I
Got I next back. Okay
And if anyone doesn't know it's like
The rumors about us and I were both very slander people and so that's why I have a codex and that's why that's why she
log some of these messages because people lie.
They lie on us and we need to prove the truth.
And so I mean, it's like, we have the truth.
I mean, it's like, so, hey, say what you want about us,
but in the end, we're trying to defend ourselves
against these insane people.
Okay, that's really good.
I got like Graham Cracker and he's a strong coffee.
Wow.
Very good
Okay, here's my cigar. Okay, so yeah, I was playing on watching a movie with a friend last night and I kind of got overwhelmed
I don't know if it was this thing. I had this little smear not watermelon
Whoa
It was pretty good now. Now. Unfortunately my lighter is it just got this lighter now. It seems like it's empty already
No, that sucks
Dang it. Yeah, it's empty. I need to light this in the stove. I'll be right back
Anyway, and so what am I saying? Oh, yep. Oh, he recorded her. Oh
Crystal oopsie
Oops crystal. Weren't you just on the salmon sister just saying you know, you weren't talking to him. So you lied to everybody
Crystal
And you bonded with Brandon. I mean
I have a little bit more very excuses. I didn't know what the fuck was up with the story right then
I was trying to figure it out and of course it went on a little look
Oh, yeah, I got I got you went on a little bit longer, but yeah, I want to hear this story
I want to hear exactly what happened because Crystal was on statements. It's really sick
Oh, no, no, I didn't talk to my I I deleted the commerce
I deleted the the group chat as soon as he got in there right there you go
So she lied so Chris you're lying. Oh my god
with Brandon. I mean, you know, I mean, after, you know, you, you knew everything. I mean, I had to do investigating about it and take me a little bit long, but it's like, you knew every, oh, well, you deserve what's coming to you, Crystal, with that, you know.
You know, I'm still facing the consequences for unintentionally doing what you did on purpose
And you know what and it's not gonna be a big deal probably for you
But it's everyone's gonna hold it against me forever at least I ever you know
It's kind of everyone always does you know, but it's okay
Hey, as long as I can I'll be sharing the truth. So
Wow. Hey guys, how are you doing? Good morning everybody. Good morning. Good afternoon or good evening
You don't see it the link I posted the link right here
It's right. See it's right here
I don't know might have to type it in manually. I did
I don't know. I don't know. Sometimes links don't come through
Anyway, you guys ever see the movie return to Oz
It's a really good movie. It's basically
It was in the 80s at stars by Rosa bulk. She's a little girl at the time
It's about
You know, it's the follow-up to the Wizard of Oz, like, you know, and Dorothy,
I mean, she's back from Oz for the first time and they think she's insane because she talks about, you know,
she's having hallucinations about, you know, the Wizard and the Scarecrow and the Cowardly Lion and blah, blah, blah, right and so
They sent her to a mental institution.
to get electroshock therapy.
Wow, that's kind of a dark turn of events for Dorothy, right?
You know, luckily there's the storm,
the clinic is hit by lightning and she escapes,
whatever, right?
Right at the nick of time.
Well, actually someone helps her escape
as this blonde patient.
Me, because look at my goosebumps,
think I'm just talking about it, your goosebumps.
Can you see them?
These are all goosebumps, okay.
Anyway.
You see I hope hopefully you can click it on it. I'm sorry
So she goes to Oz and and all the all the people that Oz has turned to stone and
All the all her friends are turned to stone and stuff like that. There's this big witch named mom be in charge
And she has a thousand heads and she goes around to these cases and I guess she took all the heads off all the all the women of Oz and
And she can put on whatever head she wants. She's like the queen with a thousand heads. Anyway, I watched that movie. It was really good. I
Used to watch it as a kid and stuff like that
Just like the original Wizard of Oz that I love the Oz movies
Yeah
Okay, so
I'm sorry. I'm sorry if you couldn't get up. I don't know. I'm gonna be drinking my coffee. I don't know
I'm gonna watch some readings. Maybe I do have to keep kind of secret the readers that I I watch because
You know, I don't want
because they're really
Because they've been telling the whole truth about everything and wow
The things I'm hearing the things I'm hearing Wow
so
Yeah, if you type StreamYard.com and then you go slash
And I'll read it to you if you if you want if you need me to read it to you. Okay StreamYard.com slash
7w
br
299 vs
If you can just type that and you're looking at the screen right there. It's there
I love this. Oh we have INX here
Hi. Oh, hey. Good morning. I had to fix my YouTube. Yeah, I'm shocked that Crystal and it's it's still playing games
She does not have a boyfriend. She's doing the same shit
She turned on Brida Chucky, who she hated for the whole year. She's insane. So she's been
in communication with Brandon when she was throwing me under the bus saying I'm buddies
with him and that he's a pedo and remember and then he kept trying to join her panels and she
kept shouting at him. She just turns on everybody. She turned on Ganville because she thought she
against them, you know, she's just insane and all she talks about is defend me. I defend you,
defend it. What is this? What's wrong with her? Why can't she do real life? It's not about
defending or fighting online. That's her whole life. You know, it's be real. You don't have a boy
friend. That guy got done with her because she always calls the cops on them all.
She's on all night long looking for making all these chat groups again and she
was hate and she likes to hate bond with people and so does Brandon because he was desperately
trying to join her panels and she wouldn't let him. I wonder what Barb would say that she was
being buddies with them talking shit about us and he's a liar. Guess what? I found out that he
uh alex on on that panel the first one that we were on he lied about that because he was telling
crystal no i i never called your dad and and something i don't know what story he made up
that he never called her okay that's fine then why lie about it i yeah the dad said she came
banging on her door and was hitting herself in the face when he tried to call the police on her
he lied about everything so now he's pissed off because she's denying him saying that he just
popped in a group chat no she makes these group chats and adds everybody to it because she's
making all these group chats to make war with people yeah and defend me defend me it's it's like
I'm completely denied.
She said, oh, well, well, this Mowgli,
or I just thought, I thought that was a joke.
I was like, is that from the Jungle Book?
I wasn't sure, I wasn't sure who she spreads with.
But yeah, I was like, okay, what are these group chats?
Like, what are the group chats?
I was like, I know, I mean, people have discord
and you know, they're conversations.
Yeah, how is there some group chats?
And IG, she's always done that.
She lives for her IG group chats.
And Discord, you know, Discord, whatever the groups are at, that's how she started with
the gambles a long time ago. But she was going there to start wars because she'd pulled me in
and had tried to get me to lie about her fake abortions and, you know, and her ex-friend
Jamie even called her out for that too. Everybody's done with her. And me and the person that was,
we were going at it for years because of them, we're fine now.
She gave me some good advice to stay off panels, you know?
She said, did you hear who's churned against Bita now?
Yeah, I'm not surprised because Vita is a bad person and like everybody says, she's probably a man, you know, she looks like a man, you know, I'm not surprised. I don't even know why she gave her a chance because Vita, I have the ICR reports and stuff that she sent me to call the FBI and she sent that to me and it was either in late February or March of 2023.
Okay, so Kristen Marie says Mogwai was the first to stick a brush of his booty on a panel.
He's a guy, he's an older guy, he's got mental issues and he was always working at Walmart.
He does, what do you call it, cleans up for Walmart or whatever, and he'd get on lives
and then he almost lost his job because they were doxing him.
I don't know, they said he's a pedo or something, I don't know anything about him, I just remember
he was a nutty guy who's always trying to get a girlfriend online because he doesn't
and he's an older guy so I don't know I've only seen him a couple times and I
saw him on Walmart because he'd be raging and yelling at Crystal because he
was at his job and it was like yeah why are you live on your job and they were
calling his job I think all right that was a long time ago so she's in
communication with them too because they had a big falling out too a long time
I mean, the woman is sick.
She's playing these games.
And, you know, Brandon recorded her like he was doing me,
recording me for his lives, remember?
He was doing that to her the whole time.
So now he's mad and he said he's gonna expose her
and everything.
Well, you know, get over it, Brandon.
You know, you're the one that wanted to reach out to her.
You knew how she was, you know?
And he's a liar himself.
Look, he lives in a shitty place, no pool, nothing.
It's a dump.
I lived in a nice apartment and I don't live there anymore. I moved in the in December
You know, and he's going on and he's just has no friends in real life, you know
And then the story that he recorded crystal saying yeah, I remember my way
They were trying to get me to date you he says that about everybody everybody. Oh my gosh
You think that he's like
Every woman in the community is
I mean, from vegan patriot, to beta, to, you know, I mean, he thinks everyone is in love with him.
And it's like, he looks like that David Wynne.
Yeah, he's crazy because I have a lot of texts and calls from vegan about him.
She's scared of him.
She doesn't want anything to do with him.
Yeah.
I'm going to show you.
I can trust you, what she had to say, that he wouldn't leave her alone, that she stalks him.
Because her and I, we've been communication and I helped her out a while ago.
you know and uh yeah she left me a lot of messages and stuff and he's it's a lot about
him i don't know if i should post it or what well but yeah he just needs to leave people alone and
you know he knows i come from money everybody knows that he doesn't have shit he's a criminal
Yeah, we'll call them out for it. So yeah, I don't know what's wrong with crystal. Why did she even give him a chance?
So he said he's gonna expose her
Yeah
I mean, I'm sure I don't really want to see crystal exposed. I mean because you know
Kind of fight a little bit. How are you gonna people have already exposed everything?
I don't want to see her nude. I'm just kidding
I don't think that's gonna happen again,
but she's the one that puts herself in it.
And why is she talking to Salmon again?
Cause yes, I saw Kate said something about
she was promoting Salmon's.
channel after she bragged about how she took down this channel.
Well, yeah, she says she was threatened by someone.
Do you know who she was threatened by?
She says somebody threatened her and she's afraid of her life.
And that's why she took down the strikes on Samman's channel.
I wonder who's threatened her.
You can't take down the strikes on Samman's channel.
She's full of it.
And that's why Kate called her out when she tried to join Kate's
with that stupid excuse.
Yeah, take it down.
Yeah.
You can take down a copyright strike because somebody did that for me one time, that a lady that exposed Crystal's past and the truth about her, she had done a copy strike and then she apologized and told me she took it off because she remembered that she did give me permission to use the ABBA video about Crystal.
She has a lot on her page about all these people so I don't know crystal is just a piece of shit
I wonder what Barb would say if she finds out that she started communicating with branding because they were screaming at me
for talking to him.
Oh, it's just actually crazy.
Well, I guess the new story with Bita is that, you know,
I guess Bita because, you know, Bita made up with Eldo or Bita still talks to Eldo.
And then, you know, the AAM woman is saying that Eldo is a, you know,
going to threatening violence and salmon, threatening violence and all these kind of things,
which is like, I'm a little bit far-fetched.
He got docs too by Pibbs.
Okay.
Aldo got completely doxxed last night three times and they doxxed his address.
Yeah, they put his address out there.
Wow, so so I guess was this so it was be the dogs like pebs to like last night
And and Ziya in and the chat they had her address all over the place. They spammed the chat with her
I wonder who's putting that in there. I don't know. I think the pebs did and then some one of their
Main characters or whatever that's another join, but they was all over the chat. It was just
Well, there's got to be a chat after chat after chat the whole whole thing was blown up with that and then Eldos address and now I'm looking it's like who's who's that who lives there and then they said it was him and they said his real name.
Well, yeah, so the theory is, I mean, I guess there's, there's some like law firm was found with like a similar last name to beta but the theory is now that beta.
is trying to bait people into like civil lawsuits
to be settled out of court or something like that.
And-
You can't do that.
She's been saying that for years.
You know, she's full of it
because a lot of people had stuff on her.
Why do you think Ashley Ray did all the stuff to her?
She had sent her a glitter bomb.
She had sent her some so much stuff.
And she could never do anything about it. You know, she'd come crying to us crying and
always begging us to help her. She's never going to change. And that's the truth about her. She
always lies and threatens lawsuits, but nothing ever comes of it. But she sent me an IC3
reporting FBI thing to do on Alex with Alex's information. And so Alex knew that. So I don't
taking her back where she knows better.
I mean, it's just, it is, hey, you got to really,
I mean, you're like a forensic,
I mean, to keep track of all of these things,
I mean, it's just, it's insane, it's insane.
And I mean, I'm gonna be really trying to like,
avoid hate bonding and that kind of thing.
It's like-
Exactly, me too.
Yeah, you know, and like I said,
the person that me, you know,
I didn't get along with has been the one
that gave the best advice.
Yeah.
And we're cool now, you know?
So I'm glad about that.
And as far as these other people,
I just don't trust any of them, you know,
the hate bonding or whatever, you know?
It's like, let's do real life like I've been doing.
Yeah, well, I'm kind of like sad because
And sure a lot of times when we're out in the world doing real life, we know that's
We have our phones and then we'll get in there and see what's going on and shit and I'm sick of that
I don't want to do that again, and I haven't done that after the talk I had with somebody that gave good advice
Yeah, she was like, wow, I just saw you on the panel. Why why don't bother with them? You know, they're not worth it
And I realized you know what you're right
I mean, I was out and then there I was on my phone getting on YouTube, you know, uh-huh
Yeah, it's it's not
worth it
and then Barry says that
Brandon keeps tagging him and he can't he can't stand him
That's why him and I had it falling out because he said do you talk into a petto and you know because they
Blasted him out already before yeah, and then he complained on a in the
Uh, he was on a panel say, oh, no, why he's
Tagging me. Yeah, they can't stand him. That's why we we stopped talking was because I was giving Brandon a chance
Well, I mean the bq person is now. I mean he keeps printing these bots in my chat to say
Oh, Brandon rejected you, is that Brandon rejected you and I?
It's him, it's just sick the bots that he has and it's obvious those are all bots and
he doesn't get it. He's even making fake DMs now, they said, K called him out called Mockley
and he made the fakest DM between him and Lindsay who's never liked him. I mean,
she just broke up with her boyfriend, her baby's daddy and
you know leave him alone but he's going on in there making it look like she's in love with him and
he posted a fake mockly uh i g dm of them okay well we have it coming up let me see if this
person's gonna behave themselves um who is it because i don't want to argue with
I love his hair though. He's got like he looks like he's looking at his neck beard though.
You like my hair? I like your hair. It's nice.
Mine is too wavy. Thank you. I appreciate it.
Face glam mother could love big right there. Yeah and the hair and that's my mommy right there.
Yeah
Like a fish you look like you look like a blowfish sick you're looking a little bit like crystal crystal land today. I
Think the word you're looking for is frog
My crystal and do you mean what's her name?
Crystal and she's like that. No, I mean Chris the crystal and it's like she does have a little bit of a trailer trash opinion
I mean appearance
Yeah, but but a Kate Kate by far. She is like the worst looking out of all the drama queens
All the mean girls that like are stuck in high school mentally
Kate is gonna be definitely as the ugliest one. She's pretty beat-looking
Well, you know like I'm not I'm not the prettiest looking. I'm not the most handsome looking guy ever, but yeah
What about these people?
Well, Bita isn't that fat.
That's why I go down.
Credit where credit is, dude.
She's not that fat.
At least not in the face.
We'll make sure.
Maybe maybe she's got a little bit of a pouch on her stomach, but she doesn't have it in her face
Okay, okay. You're in love with be do we get it? Okay? Let me see if I can okay. Yes. Yeah, right?
So this is obviously I'm gonna be biased here. Okay. Well, I do have a picture
I mean, where's my Kate picture? I mean, I had a Kate picture that I made but they had a lot of Kate's pictures up
That's sad that they did that to our so I don't yeah
It's like beat. She's like really
I made this one and this is actually based on her real picture right there. Here we go
So there you go. Yeah. No, there's no
It wouldn't be it wouldn't you don't need AI to make her look bad. No, well, I do because I
But here's the thing here's the thing that whoever I'm not sure I'm sorry whoever said that oh don't do that
so like why like
like
I don't have any allegiances. Okay. I just don't like that bitch because she always likes to bring me up
She tried like like it was like a year or two ago. I don't know a while ago
She tried to like I guess she was like bored or whatever
She like made AI images of me in her stream like she was trying to drag me into her ball of shit
So I'm I don't give a fuck about that. So
Also, she's like ugly as fuck and I roast her for that whenever she brings me up. I roast her for that
I tell her like yo, you're like bitter right cuz you're ugly, right?
So like you're ugly on the outside. So that's why you're jealous of girls like beta that are not ugly
So that's all it is. It's that simple. It's literally that juvenile
Well, how about like, you know, I did I didn't hear like, you know, Barry kind of was yelling at her about I guess
And then and then that's a crazy thing. Can you imagine being a black like honestly? I mean look
I'm a black guys. They got their advantages. There's some things right pros and cons with everything
but like damn bro like black guys they kind of like
It's funny because like
You would think like well black guy has all the options in the world
But you always see a black guy with some like like it's just not good for like just retard
Well, I mean sometimes they like the heavy sack because I think in like, you know, like well see that's what that's exactly what it is
It's it's like their curse their curse because like if unless she's fat
She's gonna be insane and retarded in the horror like they're like they kind of they can only they can
Oh, they're only option is a fatty because if it's not a fatty, it's gonna be a retarded insane or
Yeah, it's kind of it's not a good place to be really
I think that's one of my favorite appearances of you. I mean, it's like, wow, you're on fire today.
I mean, I'd like, I'm on fire every day. I don't know when you always say this,
literally every time that we have a conversation, you say this every single time.
I'm glad to see that you are still alive.
I was trolling back because, you know,
that woman Christine continually says
for me to unalive myself.
And so I was trolling back.
I'm glad that you're okay.
Thank you.
Yeah, Christine, Christine is a,
she's a bit of a, she's a bit of a loose cannon as well.
She's always, she used to,
she always used to say, stuck my ass.
She always say, stuck my ass.
Until I until I started and until I was like, oh, yeah, Christine's here to get her ass up
And she's like stop saying
Stop saying
Psyche what happened to Lenore?
Shout out to the horny old ladies that like things in their butt
You know what it's really hot inside and she's a black cat and so yeah
I mean she's been spending time outside, and then there's this dog
That is barking all the time the Norse by I just like you know and plus like I have this camera on a tripod now
And so you know you don't see around my house like you used to and stuff like I know here's Lola sleep
You're never there. Oh Lola's low psyche if you do can you just say this right now?
For future reference psyche if you are going to neck
I'm not going to make it if hypothetically right right god forbid you are gonna make arrangements
for your cats and they won't just die and and and next time next time that you threaten to
unalive yourself make sure that you tell everyone that you set up arrangements for them just do
that just be like I paid a kennel for six months and then they end up on a cell turn whatever
Well, I have arranged
There's at least three people that
I think they can go to okay, so but but I'm not gonna do that. I basically was talking about basically like my online presence
The South Park where it's like they say oh my gosh this girl like she deleted her Facebook account or something
They're like oh my god. She's dead, but it's like it's just cuz she deleted her Facebook kind of like I don't it was long that light of
No, no, but that was that's not the same thing because you you literally I forget verbatim what the words were but you said something alluding to
Allude alluding minute. Yeah. Yeah, so whatever whatever look we got our we got our scuffed Howard Stern everybody celebrate
We still have our retarded Howard Stern psyche, you know that every fucking time I
Have I have an old car one of those old cars that has a has a serious XM
Thing every fucking time that I turn the radio on I get an ad for Howard Stern
And I want to fucking eat a bullet
Yeah, because I have to I have to press the I have to press literally all I have to press like a fucking cheat code on my
Stereo to turn it off and then so I could listen to my Bluetooth
Know I mean I say they have a lot of because he's the biggest thing on serious
I guess I used to have I used to listen to that on him a lot
I guess he's not very entertaining to me anymore. Oh, bye. I and X. Thank you for being here
But they don't they don't let you they don't let you turn it off and I swear every every time you turn the car on
You hear oh subscribe to serious XM. Oh, you can listen in your phone your car and add every time
There's so many backstage. So oh, I this is her name is appreciative something hold on a second. I'm gonna put
I'm just gonna bring them up. I'm gonna put you full screen one second. That's Piranha
She
Cat killer. Oh my gosh. I think that was man a gay person. Was that a gay person?
That sounded like Piranha. She's a furry. Oh, she's a furry. She is I know
Where's the bug plug that has a furry tampon?
He does I will but look oh wow yo psyche is my friend look here's the thing
What you could do right now?
Cuz cuz right you have this person that came in and said this thing can you discuss discuss in the state of your cats?
My cats are fine. They're fine. I mean it's been said that I sacrificed Lenore to the dark
Yeah, I heard that that's crazy. I mean, I don't know look look the reality is like I'm sure you know that people do that
People have done that
I know that's not like that's stupid and I don't practice that kind of no, I'm not saying I'm not saying you do
I'm just saying it's not like implausible. It has happened before
Like people have done it. There are crazy unfortunately crazy stupid people in the world that would you have them?
But also it was also said last night that I'm trying to breed Lola so I can sacrifice the kittens and stuff
I just want to let everyone know Lola is spayed so Lola and all my all my cats are
Are spayed and so there's no way there's gonna be is it true?
Is it true that you spend all your money on drugs so you have to eat the cats for food?
That's not true. That's not true at all
Okay
So like how much of the money do you spend on like amphetamines? What money?
What do you have on money? What money the money?
There's no money. What do you mean? What's what money?
What I don't have any money
You don't just have a giant mound of money next to you. No, I wish
Okay, I have a giant
Mound of tobacco on my table. I have a he has a giant mound of debt
You know, just like your giant mound that you call a penis, um, it looks like it looks like a thick husk
I wouldn't call it a giant mound
That's very that's very generous. Okay. Remember when Christine said that her husk is bigger than your dick
I remember when she said that was that disgusting Christine. Yeah, she said her
Yeah, what does she mean her pussy has a husk? Yeah, I think it's a whole man. That's gnarly
She calls it her house.
I believe that, too.
Dang.
That's crazy.
Oh, these people.
These people sing.
I mean, it's like, gosh, I mean, I thought we were crazy, but I mean, it didn't mean it was the people.
I mean, I can't take it.
But I mean wow, so what's up with river glow? I thought he was around last night
I think he was on a show like I guess it was like money for money
That's what he uh, he um, what's the word? What's the he committed? He did a sewer
Did it you did a slide he did a slide down the sewer you remember when um, he you know
He was he was in my city and he was like called me. He's like, oh, I'll be there in five minutes
I'm gonna pick up a piece. Yeah, there you go. So you you got all scared in shit. He wanted you
I didn't realize, I didn't realize that Dina was gonna get the strap on.
Okay, that's what he got scared. I didn't get scared.
You missed out. Dina was gonna get the strap on.
Well, I don't know if I want to see there. We're gonna run a train on your psyche. You missed out. He told me he told me
He's like, yo, I'm pulling up. I'm on redondo beach. I'm gonna pull up to psyche and run a train on him
That's what they said. This is appreciative
2026 hello
Appreciate him
That's my new e-girl friend
Shut up to piranha for stalking me everywhere. Okay. I guess appreciative is not there. Okay. I
Think I thought I heard Ernie Ernie and bird lap
Who was that who was that like Midwestern woman that I was just talking to earlier
Damn she sounds like she sounds like she's from like no walking
She's only like she's from a trailer park in Milwaukee. Oh, come on leave her alone. No
No, I'm not I'm not saying like like any shout out to all these people. You know, it's crazy about the trailer park
Now trail, I guess not even cheap to live in the trailer park anymore. Now. It's like fucking thousands of dollars
Well, there's tiny homes. I mean there's tiny homes. I mean tiny homes look oh no
Those are terrible though the thing about the tiny homes, and I mean the I mean it's less of a problem in California
They're not insulated
You're just living in a metal box. It's literally just a shipping container box
You know, you can buy on Amazon for like $3,000 you can buy a house like fully like put together
Basically, it comes on a helicopter like that. Okay, we have a pretty good one. No, there's no way that would be the cost of the helicopter
Why appreciate of 2027s in the back one second. Hello show your cat show me your kids
Yeah, I don't think that was I don't think that was appreciative. They told me show me your asshole
Okay, we have slugger Sam. Yo, it's so funny yo psyche you remember when Noel got her titties on you look so disgusted that was crazy
Slugger Sam
Usually sometimes it's sneaker. I usually go by like thank you guys. This guy's an app science supporter
I remember I remember I remember is this kid. How do you see your name again? Sid?
say
Sick this guy this guy this guy's a legend, bro
This guy goes panel to panel. He'll terrorize people this guy's a fucking og bra
But shout out to psyche
Shout out to psyche bro in the building salute to the God
Thank you. Thank you. This is fun. Yeah. Thanks. You're a secret
You're one of my I just remember like, you know, you're one of my first gov
Guess that he man came up on my piano before you know, you're a cool guy risk your spiritual
You have a good insight about stuff. So how have you been? I've been in a while. Yeah. No, I've been good man
I appreciate it, bro. I've been just continuing to walk the path, you know, like just trying to get more insight
You know and it's good to be around people like you because I remember you gave me a reading
You gave me a reading when you know along. I think it was like two years ago
Maybe two and a half years ago. I think it was you gave me a reading and it was a really good reading, you know
But that's all I'm doing right. I'm just
I'm just trying to continue to walk the path.
That's great. Awesome. Yeah. Me too.
And that's like, you know, that's kind of like, you know, I got,
I think, you know, something really to devote, you know,
one's life to because it is a long, it's a long, it's a lifelong or
lifetimes long.
Pursuit and you know, I think that's where the real fulfillment can come is is through these
You know the the most valuable things are things that you can't see that are things aren't the normal things the things that aren't things, right?
It's like so great
Go talk to sing for a second. I'm your back. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I was gonna
You know, I was gonna ask psyche about cuz I know earlier you want the Starbucks
I was and I wanted to ask him what should I get I normally get a nice coffee
But psyche psyche was getting me all excited about the the new
Frappuccino and all so I gotta figure out. What's your psyche? What should I get other than a nice coffee? What should I get?
This is a Frappuccino, but this is a S'mores Frappuccino, so it has like marshmallow cream, it has like the chocolate, it has, um, it has graham cracker, um, topping in it, and then I have a couple, I add a couple shots.
Okay, so we have Cash Cove, okay, this guy looks interesting.
Go to a, go to a local coffee shop.
Hi.
No, no, I'm Starbucks all the way.
I'm going Starbucks room.
Look at this guy, Cash Cove.
How are you?
Oh, yeah, if you can go to a local
I remember one time. I remember growing up one time. I was like some friends house and
We're talking about getting pizza
Yeah, and then and then his dad was and then we're talking about getting Papa John's pizza
He was like, oh, what the his dad was like, oh, why would you do that?
Like don't get corporate pizza get local pizza. I was like, yeah
Yeah, look at this guy cash you talk to a local business
Support local business
You're kind of hot
You can't even see him or her. You can't even tell
Are you a guy? Maybe it's a femboy. Maybe it's a femboy. He likes it in the ass
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I thought you were a hot guy. No, no, no, no, no, no, psyche psyche. I also
I also thought it was a guy, but then when it laughed, I was like, it's giving girl.
I don't know who it is, but I don't trust this person with a hundred gallons of nitroglycerin.
Wow.
Okay, well, you have a full look though.
Are you in the military by chance?
No, it's like a cosplay.
Okay, cosplay.
Okay
And we've got the FBI director cash Patel the guy that always
He looks like he's on man what you said everybody always says that what do you mean?
Oh, yeah. People say that they call you cash Patel. Exactly. That's great. So you're really
on some fed shit, huh? I don't know. Shit. Good thing I have a good thing. I have a giant
a tattoo under my scrotum. That's my allegiances. I'm a real communist. What do you think to
I thought you were in the game of thrifts.
No, I was communists.
It is weird Chris the Chris summary. I know it's weird. I know this is weird, but you know what? I like weird. It's weird
Yeah, it's weird because I'm a Republican voter. I'm a Republican voter for all the girls I guess they're all in T4
Yo, Jay dog, what do you think about that? I'm a Republican voter. I have water for Trump 2027
And all the girls that fuck with me, they're all Antifa.
How do you feel about that?
Cash, are you an adult?
I just want to make sure.
Are you an adult, Cash?
Yes.
Okay, Cash is an adult.
Okay, thank you.
You are a female, right?
Wait, what did you say?
Okay, it's me personally. I bought it for trunk 20 27
All the girls that fuck with me, they're all antifa they all they all think that I'm a racist
Yo, what does it say? What does it stay on the patch next to the flag?
What does it say?
That's such a gay pass really
Lower his mic bro, look at this. I thought it was gonna be something cool like a
Okay, can you hear me now psyche? Okay. Okay. How are you psyche bro? I've been seeing everything that's been going on
Dude, I you know what yesterday, I hope you're not mad yesterday. I get a wellness check on you, bro
I don't know if anybody came and knocked on your door or anything like that because I was worried you said you know last day on earth
okay um yeah um so what else is up okay so yeah okay so i hope we don't have a master tutor in the cast
um are you a master tutor or a cast?
so like he has another john smith situation
oh what you're on smith by the way
okay what's going on saver cash where are you from cash
Dude, this is a kid.
Who is a kid?
Goodbye.
How old are you?
Okay.
Man, psyche always doing some apstein shit.
Oh, shut up.
I mean, I don't know cash. Well, if that is if that is a teenager they need to find a better hobby
What are they they're trying to did cosplay and column mine?
You're gonna be playing Columbine. That's crazy. How's my audio? How's my audio?
Okay
Know cash if you can just like you know everyone just for something
I just need to like make sure you're adult because it's like you know, there's weird shit that goes on
So so okay, so hopefully everyone's like he's running in Epstein Street
Did you send that person to come here and then now for you to say what you're doing?
Are you like, uh, are you trying to do an ensrapment thing here? Is that what's going on?
So now you're trying to, now you're trying to
Sick, did you send that individual here?
So now, so now you're trying to explore me.
Are you trying to strike this channel that we live?
Are you on off, bro?
Are you a two-faced dog?
So that's what, so that's what you're doing, bro?
That's the word doing that.
Is that what you're doing, bro?
Are you in the ops, bro?
So now you're trying to explore me.
I would have put across that this sick fella sent that individual here so he can do what
he did to you.
I would have put it across to him.
Yeah, I would have put it across to him.
Okay, they have an ID. Okay. Okay. I take the ID. It's good. Okay. You can put it down. You can put it down
I'll let you back up. I'll you back up. I see the ID
Put it down so you don't see that. Okay. There we go. Okay. Cash is an adult
Thank you. Don't get it. Yeah, that's good. Okay
Okay
It's okay. You put it down cash put it down put it down
No, don't yeah, don't show your ID. Don't don't dog. Don't dog yourself cash. Don't dog yourself
That's what we're saying. We don't want you doxing yourself, right? Yeah
Okay
Okay guys, okay, did I kick off today? Are you still left? Okay, so I
Ran him off. I ran him off
Good. Well, thank you. Thank you. Thank you so much because you know, I had no problem. It's so loud
Oh, he's he's he's just a vicious, you know animal. Yeah, he goes panel to panel just cooking people bruh
Yeah
So what's up today for everybody? It's Sunday Sunday. Um, we have the rest of the weekend ago. How are we? So I I have to call in sick
Psyche and I'll tell you why and Psyche, please forgive me. I haven't even asked about you
And I'm sorry, but but I'll answer this and I want to know what's going on with you
But I called in sick because Thursday. I for some reason ended up getting a swollen thumb
Couldn't sleep all a Friday all a Friday night. I couldn't sleep, but I still want to work and then last night
I said the hell with this. I'm calling in sick. I can't so now I just left the doctor's office
And I got a I got an antibiotic for my thumb
Because it's all fucked up, but thank you. I gotta ask about you man. What's going on with you, bro?
I thank you. I hear you you're cooking people left right and center breath
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like I got it because getting you started left right in center
Yeah
Hold on. Hey, sir. So when I'm talking a psyche, I want you to shut the fuck up. You got that though
You're not psyche last time I checked yo
Everything that you're saying you got to talk to my friend. Let me talk to my friend psyche and you shut the fuck up
You got it
Wow
They people lie on me and I actually tell the truth about people and so and I do believe the truth is always
Stronger than than fiction, right?
narratives of me eating my cats, killing my cats, sacrificing them to Satan, you know,
trying to gather power, me extorting blackmailing people, me, all the stuff that you're all,
hey, rumors of my death have been highly exaggerated. Yeah, yeah, that was crazy. I don't know, I'm
sorry guys, I mean, before that person appointed, they got a cash, yeah, next time no weapons on
Um, wow. Yeah. It's like, but you know, I'm hanging in there, right? I'm hanging in there and uh,
no, everything's okay. Everything's okay.
Thank you. Here's what you got to remember, my friend, right? When they can't, when they have
nothing against you, that's when they resort to making rumors up. That's, that's just their,
their, their classic. That's what they've been shown to do, taught to do.
And that's that's what they resort to
You know I mean psyche that's what they resort to see I would rather people tell the truth about me
I would rather people say oh, you know and he he did that and if I really did it that I'll own up
But people in general nowadays they got to make up rumors
They got to make up lies right and it shows their character
That's what you got to remember. It shows their character.
I've been on, you know, I'm on camera. I show myself. I show my house. I mean, I've shown everything about myself and it's like,
yeah, but it's this troll who don't tell the truth about themselves, just lie. And then it's like, and sometimes they're even they're
they're believed because over me, because I don't know, people like to believe like the like the the worst about things.
not a person that wants to harm anybody, harm anybody. I mean, I don't know. So it's all,
it's all just lies and, you know, the people that know me understand that and the people that don't,
they, they won't understand anyway, you know, so, but I, because they fall for anything.
They fall for anything. So, Jackie, I've never, I'll tell you this, and I've known you for,
like I said, a little over two and a half years now. I've never, ever,
Look to you in a bad image like oh this this psyche guy is a snake or he's no good
Nothing. I you ask anybody at all these youtube streets
Never ever have I ever said a bad thing about psyche got the utmost respect
Because psyche have always given us your platform to come here to talk shit be who we are
Get to know who we are and a lot of people that see the problem is psyche
The only thing i'm going to blame you for is
You don't put your foot down enough with these people some of these people you gotta know when to tell them shut the fuck up
Because when you give them an inch
Sorry, when you give them an inch they take a mile
That's how a lot of them are
And then they take they try and take advantage of good people like me good people like you
You know, they don't know how to just be appreciated
I had some psyche you'll never believe what happened the other day, but I have to cut somebody off and they
They were victimizing themselves
They're like, oh you're you're typical. You're just like everybody else and I said no
No, I said I see the problem with you. I see the problem with you. Yeah
But no accountability psyche, you notice that they don't want to take accountability and
I didn't like what that lady said about you the other day on your panel channel
I heard her sit calling you
Messed up names and I said, yeah, you know what?
You know what bro, she should I'm talking about that Vita lady. I think it's Vita. Is it Vita is her name?
Things about my family my mom my deceased father
And uh and and and his lies. I mean she's I mean she's just full of shit and uh, you know, she's disgusting
She's disgusting bro. Is that what she called you?
What she called you was horrific and I said look how the hell are you gonna call a man that when you know that?
That's one of the crimes where there's no coming back from
Like and you don't have paperwork to back it up
Like you should be in jail for that beta beta should get locked up for accusing you of that
It's like all accusations are just flying rampantly without any proof evidence and it's like the worst thing is that people that you know just blindly believe it but it kind of sorts out you know the trash takes itself out and they just reveal themselves and then I decide not to platform them you know.
I know, it's unfortunate, like I used to be friends and I never did anything about that woman as like, she actually, it came out that she gave my phone number, my bank information, my address to like a known criminal doctor, you know, and, you know, out of revenge, and then she says you're gonna do that kind of thing, and then she, now she keeps denying it, then she finally said, well, I did it, but I don't care that I did it.
Wow.
And so I mean and then nobody really else cares like it may as like but I'll keep telling you the truth about it and
No, that's the things like you you got people like me who definitely do care who definitely are
Absorbent to what's going on. You know the streets like it's kind of like what I can't eat those seven can't eat those way
He said the streets. He's watching and the streets. He's talking
You know and we see it bro
I like people you know the only reason why people don't get involved and do what I'm doing right now and kind of routes for you
It's because they love the drama right they'd rather see the drama
You know continue to play mom and get bigger and bigger. They don't want to they don't want to do what I'm doing
We're just trying
expose people for being phonies.
They don't want to do that.
You know what I mean?
All right.
So there is cash.
Thank you.
I don't know.
Yeah.
OK.
So there's Tranny Psyche is coming.
There's one named Tranny Psyche.
Let's see who this person is.
One second.
Tranny Psyche?
Tranny?
Psyche.
You are a diddler.
You were liking little boys on TikTok.
Don't fucking lie to these people.
And then depending on you as a piece of shit.
Who is this?
OK.
Can you please provide the proof of that?
Okay, provide evidence. Yeah, so no evidence. Provide evidence, right? Yeah
Crazy crazy, and you can only see the reason why that guy can do that on the internet
is because, unfortunately, the law allows them to do this type of dumb shit and not have any consequences.
Right. You know what I'm saying?
I have talked to the police before about some of these things, and I've even had people, like, you know, threatening physical harm against me, blah, blah, and I've told the police, and the police say, that was Archie's real voice, wow, yeah, yeah, and, yeah, the police say, well, through to him, speech.
and I was like, well, you know, it's the day that you're gonna, you know, I'm
harm somebody, you know, making threats that saying that you won't go to jail if you do
something to me because I'm just a bad person and that kind of thing, which is crazy. Yeah,
that was RG, that was crazy. You know, you know what, Psyche, let me, let me tell you this real
quick about that, right?
The a lot of the cops are fucking ignorant to the law
That's why they'll arrest somebody in the case gets dropped when he says it's freedom of speech
There's a fine line between defamation of character and free minute freedom of speech psyche
So a good lawyer a really good lawyer would be like freedom of speech my fucking ass
This case has got defamation of character already and over it and that person
Such as bitch boy that just got on the panel saying admit it that guy doesn't realize he can get sued really really bad
We're talking about we're talking about money that his fucking ancestors or sorry that
You know that his descendants are gonna be paying out the ass till the day they die
That's what I'm talking about bro
So the law does not care that you're ignorant and the law unfortunately hires ignorant cops all the time
Don't know what the fuck they're talking about dude. I've seen you ever can't you ever watch like ski ski John
You know Skeeter John
Yeah, he's a youtuber based
I believe in the Michigan area and he kind of does what Chris Hansen did like he catches predators
Dude, you know how did like most cops right away comply and they're like alright
We'll arrest the guy and have the detectives look over all the evidence you gathered up for us
Because he pretty much does all the work for the cops and all the cops have to do is arrest the guy
But there have been a handful of cops who would say
We can't arrest this person. They haven't broken a crime and he told me what are you talking about?
We got messages where the guy shows his private parts
To what he believed was you know blah blah blah and he told blah blah blah. He was gonna do this dirt
And that's right and this is what i'm saying. You've had some cops
Who have defended the chomo or the predator or whatever so cops
What i'm saying is when you're calling a cop and they're saying freedom of speech
Wouldn't believe that I take that shit to a lawyer and say hey, let me sue these motherfuckers
Let me let me make it. Let me make some money off it. Let me make an example bro, you know
Yeah, you don't remember Nicki Minaj. You don't remember Nicki Minaj sued a youtuber for them a definition of character
You don't remember that bro. Yeah
Yeah, I believe it was I believe it was north north of a million at least it was north of a million
For a youtuber she was able to sue a youtuber. Yeah
Well, yeah, and so it's like people should I mean if they say something they should say allegedly or they should
Not say it at all or I mean they should have proof. I mean, it's like right. Yeah
So yeah, for some reason you're a smart man. I agree of you are a smart man, you know, and
I'm actually blessed to have you up here and
They're cool guy. Thank you. Thank you for sticking with me. I know I know it's it's been a wild ride
And sometimes around here. It's you know, it gets crazy
But it's always nice to have have a people like get it and you know
You're one of those people that get it and I appreciate you. Oh, no problem, bro
No problem any time and you're you're likewise to your psyche. I'd say you're intelligent yourself
You know your intelligence. It's just it all you know what it is psyche. I study psychology, right?
I did and that's what your name is your name is psyche
Psychology study of the soul. That's what it is. Yeah, it's you. I'm talking to psychology right now
But you know what what I love about it is it's a cheat code in life when you study it because you get to understand
human behavior
And what and you get to read everybody like a book, right? Like you just that's the best things like you
I'll just sit there and let people talk and be like
And they were just bullshitting
They're big like the other person the other day when they start victimizing themselves and they said I'm like everybody else
And I said look dude if you're willing to give me a minute honest to God no hard feelings nothing against you
You told me yourself. You're having a hard time making friends
And I can explain to you why you're not making any friends. I see the behavior patterns in you
Right, for instance, like you this person calls calls you five times a day every fucking day
Right, and then and then when you pick up the phone
They'll talk to you for 40 seconds and run it right away be like I gotta go I gotta go
It was it's just a lot of like these kind of bizarre behaviors
um
And then like lies about driving
Even though I know this person doesn't drive and they're they lie about driving and saying they need a ride to get some water
right
It's a lot it's a lot
But I would be like look I know what you're doing and it calls me from a private number
When I don't answer the five calls a day. Yeah
Yeah, you know the type right and it's like you don't want to listen. I said look I I know what's going on
I'm willing to help. I'm even willing to be a friend, but but it ended then and there and I was glad I said I don't need this
Stalker individual in my life. I really don't I really don't psyche
Yeah, and it's like, you know, it makes it so easy to stalk nowadays with the internet.
I mean, it's like even mean, like even people have their cameras on, it's basically like
almost like a surveil and like almost like, you know,
you're doing surveillance at yourself because people can like all of a sudden like just like
be spying and looking at all the little details in your backyard and try to come up with these
conclusions and saying this and this and this about about you and all I'm doing is basically
showing myself you know being you know and are these people showing themselves no I mean it's
like they usually don't even have an avatar if you like you're in the twilight zone and she
can't meet you sometimes what the hell just happened I'm not sure oh we have RG here what
I don't know. Okay. So one second RG. I'll let you write I'll let you write up one second
I don't see you in chat RG because I had you in blocks, but what's up? It's me
Yeah, I just came up to let everyone know that INX we're diapers. This has been confirmed
Okay, well, I don't want to have any slander and you know, okay, so I mean that's ridiculous.
You just want to come up for that.
That was kind of dumb.
Okay.
Yeah.
Ridiculous.
And you know what?
Silly, silly, silly.
Wow.
Very silly.
Wow, well, well, I want to pull you a few cards because I have I have I mean these are just some quick oracles
You're gonna do me a reading psyche. You're gonna do me a read. Oh, thank you. Thank you
No, no problem. These are these are quick oracles, but hopefully there's a good message for you in here
First we have this one says twilight. Okay. We have twilight the twilight card. This one says
surrender surrender to the last hour
where the light barely touches the flowers.
And so maybe there's something significant about tonight
or in that time of day between the day and the night
and in these board places.
Okay, we have INX coming back up, let's welcome INX.
Yeah.
I think Steven wears diapers
and his information is out there.
He's scared of that group that's after him.
Okay, you know he wears diapers because I've never I'm I'm in my early 60s. So he's full of shit. I'm very healthy piece of shit
He's gonna lose his podcast and everything
Kiwi farms. That's that's the one that's offering money for him. Okay. Yeah, so he where yo I next can I ask you a question though?
Yeah, go ahead
Like respect like respectfully though, like do you like it in the ass?
It's like a scientific question like cuz cuz it's because I give you if you
do more anal sex it could be you might need diapers like that
i think steven likes that but you have to take off his diapers i mean he's so stupid
He's a piece of shit and and he's so stupid. He doesn't even know who's the one that docks his entire information to us
But yeah, he's a piece of shit. So yeah, I think he likes it up his ass. I think he fucks his dog
That that pitbull
You know, but I'll put all his information out there. I'm putting it everywhere else
But yeah, the Kiwi farms once and bad, man, I joined them. I joined them
But yeah, he's so stupid. He has no life
You know
Yeah, I next can I ask you I next can I ask you a question real quick
What what part of the wood like what you don't have to say like what state but like what like what region of the country?
I was born in New York, but I grew up overseas because of my dad's job with the old business, so we
And my mom isn't from the state. So, you know, so I speak three languages
English is my third Spanish. It's brilliant Spanish is my first
second is um,
Portuguese brazilian Portuguese. Oh, nice. Okay. Nice. That's awesome. New york. Were you born in?
I
They said Richmond Hospital, you know, they got borrows borrows or whatever they call it over there
Yeah, five borrows five borrows. Yeah, I don't I don't so I
So you are a military brat. No, my dad in the oil business mobile oil. No
He made a lot of money. Yeah, so we
travel the world and so that's why so that's why like you could never like make friends because
everywhere you go you're changing your friends not really because everybody's stating communication
we moved to the same places in the states like uh one neighbor i knew him in bolivia
Um and and we your reality Nancy shot out to you, but I always think it's sad
Are you gonna let her talk?
Are you gonna let her talk are you gonna keep cutting her off? Are you gonna ever let her talk?
You cut her off every 10 seconds from every 10 seconds you cut her off
keep in touch all the way to adulthood and they have a big Facebook group that my
family's involved with and so we visit each other everybody still travels
everywhere and there's a bunch of them here now as adults
where I'm at it's like so we lived everywhere a lot of them you know we moved to the states and
we were neighbors in the states in different states and then we'd go back overseas and
there they were our neighbors again you know pretty much close people the group of old companies
and family stay in touch and all so yeah we still see each other and my sister's best friend
from overseas just passed away with cancer six months ago
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that, I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, and she was way younger than me.
I can't believe that was sad.
Yeah.
So everybody stays in touch and visit each other and everything.
So yeah, you don't miss those people.
And then there's the internet though too.
Oh, the internet is crazy, the internet is crazy, yeah, but it was beautiful, I just
hate the states, it's the states that we all hate, oh they're so beautiful, she looks
like the baby, the cat that I got, I call her baby right now, no I'm naming her Kitty,
like Kitty who passed away at age 20, oh yeah.
She's so cute psyche. Yeah, that baby looks just like my baby here. She's so tiny still
Yeah, I got a little weeks. Yeah, I mean, I think these cats are I mean
Okay, cats kind of like they do have person, you know
They kind of like the different colors of cats you have these personalities like I've noticed like these blood like certain black cats that are just so
so like affection and and and
and they are. Yeah, Lola is very affectionate too. She likes to go into the covers with me
and cuddle and to purrs and she actually she did have five kittens and now it's really sad because
now it was said yesterday by the AM person that I'm just going to try to get her pregnant again
so I can sacrifice the kittens and stuff like that and I have a pet cemetery and that kind of thing.
It's pretty safe and Lola is big, so psyche.
Get him.
It's the whole thing is she's big.
You just fixed I and I.
Okay.
Yeah, she's big.
All my cats are spate.
And so, I mean, it's like, that's just a narrative
that they keep trying to say that I don't,
I mean, I did, she did have one litter of cats
a couple of years ago, you know,
and that's where, you know, Tricks was one of her cats.
And, and, you know, but she had four males, one female and.
you know, male cats tend to wander and stuff. But like boy cat and I got to get him fixed. I got him
his vaccinations and stuff, but I got to get him fixed. And then the baby, she just finished her
first heat. I didn't even know she was old enough to have a heat already. She was in heat last week.
I mean, yeah, like very young, a kitten can always have kittens, which is so crazy. You know, it's like
because they say you can, you can get a spade, I guess, when they're like three months old and
stuff like that. Right. Yeah, because she's barely four months old. I think, you know,
that's what the vet said. She thinks she's about four months old. So I'm going to get it done next
week. I'm waiting on the crate that I ordered. It takes five days to be delivered because I have
her, I need to have her in the crate to recover because, you know, I have my pecanese and my other
So, I'm going to do that. And then the boy cat, I named him Elvis Elvis. Yeah, somebody said name him Elvis. He still answers the boy cat.
So he's going to be next. So, yeah, I get him fixing. I don't want any babies and.
I have all my pets and everything and they're happy, but you the black one that the one that became a bully
That's jealous of other cats. He likes to sleep. I'm not not he it's a she she likes to sleep under the covers too
She loves it. You like any of the covers come
Oh, she cuddles. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I love my fur babies and they're healthy and they're great and I have all of them.
Okay. And my Pekingese too. So yeah, but yeah, that RG guy is just a weirdo. Nobody likes Steve. I mean, his information's all out there.
They even did a picture of his driver's license, psyche.
Did you know that?
Did he show his driver's license to somebody?
Because they sure as hell posted it yesterday.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, they posted his driver's license.
I mean, they're over there doxing everybody
and Bita's information was doxed all over a chat yesterday,
last night, and they were just putting it all in there.
And I don't know what they're sending pizzas and stuff.
Yeah.
It's just insane.
but yeah just do you psyche like you were doing and yeah and and Lenore she's beautiful i hope i
see her again but yeah she's like she's right outside most of the time she's like kind of like
i like you know she's just uh she's keeping she's kind of keeping guard right now because you know
there's some kind of strange energies around like that and there's also this dog that the
Hi baby. Like mine are obsessed with my Pekingese. They love my Pekingese. They sleep together and
you know and they have their own room. I moved in December. Nobody knows my address. I moved in
December into townhouse and there's two bedrooms upstairs and one room is for them with their cat
trees and their tunnel and toys and stuff and they love it. That's where they mainly hang out
Well, I'm so happy that you have you have your kitty cat. I know it's like this is the first time you really had cat
He said oh you're kissing me. I mean, I've had them for a few years and you know that the baby is new, you know
And yeah, and then when I did get sick or whatever, you know, my sister they didn't want them fed or anything
So I
Had a find a way to get out here to get them fed or whatever
But the management worked with me and they seemed to care
Um, you know, she just hates, she hates cats because they told me then if anything ever happens with it to you, we'll take your peeking ease, but we're not taking any cats.
You know, they're, they, they hate cats.
Yeah.
Well, it's like, you know, it's like, I think that, you know, cat.
Good.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess we're like more of a dog culture, but I just love the cats. Yeah, so it was another cover late next to her. Yeah.
The one thing that was upsetting was when my sister came over after I came out of the was discharged.
And all and she and my cats were coming outside of my room and she was like, Oh my God, you still have the cats.
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh my god
Did you see, um, did you see
There's fucking Call of Duty, bro
This is the second time in the past hour
Don't come out here, don't come over here
with that shit on
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
It's okay, no you're fine
Did you ever see that clip by an actor?
I ain't no domestic terrorist, bro
I swear
I'm not, I swear.
You see the clip of my next, the Sandman, his dad.
Huh?
That's a what?
I can't hear you.
Hold on one second.
One second.
I have a clip of Sandman's dad yelling at him
to clean up the papers on his table.
Have you seen that clip?
Yeah, I've seen that clip before.
Yeah, that's his dad.
Yeah.
Yeah, let me see what there's there's a channel called salmon and friends. Okay. Have you heard of this channel's new channel?
Yeah, it's somebody that's putting stuff on on
Salmon on that channel. I don't know who that is. Yeah, let me see if I can find a good clip
There's a few clips on that channel, but I mean, I think there's one where he's crying about something
Let me hear see if I'm a salmon and friends
I just they're just short like little clips if I can play it real quick. So this one is called salmon and friends. Okay, got it
Okay, and this is called
Okay, Sam and Crash is out on Trip Kicking.
It's emotional over lyrics.
So let's hear this.
The video may be inappropriate for some users.
Okay, here we go, proceed.
Okay, so this is from the Sam and Friends channel.
He's gonna be crying and fighting with Trip and Sip,
which is always, I love to hear Sam and Cry actually.
So here, let's see, let me see, okay.
Oh, okay, one second, Cash, there you go.
Okay, let's see, Sam and Friends, allow.
okay so select this window okay um no they don't care this is trolls you see this
She's a kid, the fuck?
Do I sound like a fucking kid? No, I don't.
The fuck.
There's a lot of weird people trying to add me on IG though, Psyche.
They're just like trying to make you look like a pedophile because they're all fucking crazy.
Right, right, you know, I mean, I mean, it's like, you know, that's what they were saying. Oh, this person in the chat is
Tell it. I mean, it's like
There's not unfortunately, there's not like an ID process, but you know, just going it's a gift kind of like
go based on, I mean, talking to people and stuff.
So.
That person, Hammer, he was doxxed a couple of years ago.
He's the one that had a sex change
and his right to be deflated.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. What the fuck?
The right boob deflated. The right boob deflated after the sex
boob. That's crazy. Fitching about it. And I remember KK even made fun of him and and
called it out. It's like a girl. I shared it that he was uh from a man to a girl.
Oh wow. He went oh he had a he had a sex change. He had a sex change. Yeah. And his right boob
I mean, yeah, I wouldn't be, I mean, if my boob would deflate it, you know, but yeah,
I mean, what, what do they fill it with air or something like that?
I mean, I've had surgery, whatever they did, I don't know, deflated is all I know and cake
is called like a boob implant, basically, he was complaining about the boob deflating
and then we're making fun of him and I share that and, and hammer got pissed.
Yeah.
Yeah. Well, I was thinking it was Hebrew hammer, but I guess it's not the Hebrew hammer person.
No, not Hebrew hammer. He just went by hammer and he used to be Carissa's control as mod.
And he used to fuck with this other streamer that called him out and, you know, and, you know, it's just some weirdo him and J. R. R. They were both like girlfriends or each other or whatever I next you are never 450 pounds.
That's what someone in chat is saying.
No, I was 220 pounds.
220 pounds in 2016 and you saw me.
A little tooth man and everybody's seen me, you know? Yeah. I'm in great shape. I'm tan,
I go to the pool. And I was thin my whole life until then and my mom died and I just let myself
go. I was doing all kinds of drugs and I blew up. I was drinking tons of sodas a day.
You know, so yeah, and then I was getting diabetes and high blood pressure all that's been gone since 2017
So this is 2026
People have seen me. I look different
So I'm back to being thin like I was before I got fat
Plus I was a racquetball
semi-pro player in college and
Did the the bicathons every year they don't have that anymore though psyche that kind of sucks
The bicathons they used to have that especially when I lived in Albuquerque. They had I used to do the 50 mile
Bicathons and it wasn't racing or anything. It was just like for fun. I just like to complete it
So there that's the truth
And you see me shit
Yeah
And I've been showed somebody you know yesterday the tan and it's what the one of my enemies
You know because I'm dark now, too. I like the tan
Hammer and Chad is talking, you know, so hammer on your boobin your boob deflated. Yeah, the right
Played it. I have that video still you I'm gonna see it because it was
KK calling him out KK. I think
What's her name? Kate? All of them were calling her out because they let me share it, you know? I donated to KK.
Yeah, I even talked to Carissa time-to-time. Why did hammer turn on Carissa?
I mean is she fat now don't they saying she's fat and this was just a few years ago that she was fat me that was over 10 years ago
Hammer doesn't man. I have one boob. You didn't know that's what they're saying
Ended up with one boob because the other one deflated and he she was crying about it. I have the video I can repost it again
I save everything
All you have to do is like get that fixed. Like it's not that hard. Yeah, I guess you can get it fixed. I don't know
I mean
Well, yeah, you just get a bicycle pump
I guess you put it in the nipple and you just need to pump it back up, right?
I don't know
Well, I don't know if you have surgery don't they try to make it real I don't think you're gonna be carrying a pump around
I don't.
How does that happen?
Carrying a pumper.
Oh, hang on.
My boobs going to deflate.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
You know, I mean, unfortunately, I do see like in the chat,
being a little bit of a bully, but, you know,
INX is actually a very, very nice person.
I've actually known.
I've done some shit in the past.
Like a lot of people have.
Yes.
During COVID. Yeah. I was a bitch. And I was,
I was so into doing all kinds of drugs.
I was a bitch.
And I did some shit for some streamer who was doing a lot of
And it was stupid, but I'm sober now, three years.
I smoke weed though, when I can, and vape.
That's it, as far as the other shit.
Maybe that's why I started losing weight though too because then
You know some wiki info they contacted my kid brother to say that I've been my meth all this time
And then all of a sudden my brother turned against me saying is that how you'd lost all that weight through the years
You're doing meth and you have a friend named Larry the meth head. I said I don't know any Larry the meth head
I said they mentioned an amber. Were you looking at YouTube and he said yes
Wow, and yeah, that's when he told me so I had to block him. I was in you know
And then when I finally was discharged,
I went straight to this place the next morning
to confront him though, you know?
I mean, he was an asshole and I told him, look at me.
Do I look like I've done meth?
I said, look at my face though, you know?
I said, I got sick and it was a problem
with my right kidney.
I hadn't been drinking enough water.
It affected me.
I got sick and, you know,
and then I was hooked up to machines
and I see you for a week, but I made it.
you know, and they tell me still be careful, especially with the heat, because of my right
kidney. It didn't have enough water, so I need to drink more water than, you know, most people do
to be okay, I guess, so I've been doing good, though. I don't know about Larry the meth head,
but have you heard of Larry the cable guy? I think they messed up the name. He keeps saying Larry the
I kept telling him after because it's been months now and I keep telling him
there's I don't know Larry the method uh they have an amber he's I don't give a fuck but you
know you you must have been I thought you were doing math but when I went to see him in person the
next day because he was screaming at me on the phone with this bullshit then as soon as I uh discharge
I went straight over there the next morning to confront him though you know and tell him look
I can't believe you did this when I'm in the hospital.
And he looked at me and he goes, and he looked relieved.
And he goes, you know what, Karen, I was kidding.
And I said, no, you weren't.
I said, you were going by these stories
of whatever whoever reached out to you with.
And then he hugged me and he said, I'm sorry.
And he said, I'm sorry.
He said, I was just scared because I
did have a drug problem before.
And I've been sober for three years.
So we have a great relationship now, believe it or not, but he has a horrible temper like my dad did, and that's what I worry about.
It's really bad.
But other than that, he's a sweetheart.
He's making six figures and he's workaholic.
And my mom, her dad was a politician in Bolivia.
That's why, you know, they left us a lot of money.
And I have my own 401K plan with a lot of money,
but I don't think I'm gonna retire.
You know, I think I'm wanting to go back to work in September.
Oh, wow, I might go back to my job. Yeah. And I've been doing volunteer work at that facility. I was at and I way younger lady, you know, she was in there too. And, you know, she was in the physical rehab with me and she had had a stroke.
They said she was 51 and it looks like she had another one.
but they're saying she's going to be there for quite some time though you know and and it's
sad it's like what do i do i mean i go there once a week but i'm going to go back to work
you know while i can because i am healthy right now i just got to take care of my
right kidney and pay attention and listen to my doctor
you know so that's it
But I love animals and they're the world to me and the reason was because when I almost lost my life the first time at age 3.
It was a feral dog that saved my life.
Wow.
And ever since then, I was into animals, you know, and when I tried to learn English on
my own, because my dad used to be crazy and used to hit me when I was too demanding that
I read the doctor's book, the doctor's Swiss book in English, and I didn't know English,
you know, and I was three and yeah, so something happened and I ended up in the hospital and
and ever since then I was obsessed with helping feral dogs mostly and when I'd go outside to
play with the dogs because I was too young to go to school I was the youngest kid um American
kid there because our neighbors the American kids they were older so I'd go sit with the
feral dogs and pretend I would speak learning English because I felt safe with them you know
Wow, and so all my life is they come first before any human being
You know including family, you know, I love my family. They're the world to me, but animals come first
And that's why oh
So, yeah
Like damn yo cash, why are you hiding your face? I'm not a police officer
it's a lot it had to do with like my dad or whatever and you know and and it's just too much on a
three-year-old and almost lost my life and I don't know it's weird because when I had to call this
aunt in in Portugal to tell her about my mom that my family said you need to tell her that your
mom passed away and I thought well I remember we visited her when I was three
And that's right after I had whatever accident,
but I don't remember her.
And I just remember a few bits and pieces
of what was happening there with me and my mom and her
and they were crying and they were something about my dad.
But I never, I don't remember her.
I've never seen her since or anything.
And then when I had to be the one to call her about my mom,
she was just stunned like quiet.
She didn't say anything like she was shocked
I was alive or something.
And I said, and I was speaking to her in Spanish and then we spoke Portuguese and she said all you remember Portuguese and it's like, I don't remember you.
But yeah, I had to be also your Brazilian.
Uh, no, she, no, my mom, she was, uh, she was mostly Spanish, um, but her sister moved,
yeah, they moved to Brazil.
They speak Portuguese.
I don't give a fuck, Cass.
Yeah.
So we learn Portuguese to my mom.
Nager.
Hey, Steve.
Yeah, that was weird and we started speaking Portuguese, but she sounded shocked that I was alive and then my sister, you know, she hates my mom's family because she said, Karen, you better never talk to her again.
You need to block her because they're trying to get in our lives and stuff, you know.
And I don't know it's weird and it's like, it's my life. I should have how many years ago was this 100 years ago.
Brazil's not in Brazil.
How long ago was this?
Portugal and Brazil are not the same place.
When my mom died, that wasn't that long ago.
They speak Portuguese and Brazil, yes or no?
Brazil, yes, but it's a little different
than the Portugal and Brazil.
They speak Portuguese, yes or no in Brazil?
Yes. Yes, Portuguese.
But there's a difference.
Yo, Cache, has anybody ever told you
that you look like Blackout Andy?
I don't look like blackout India. Are you kidding me? You see my profile picture. That's what I was in college.
I'm pretty much feel like nobody's talking about you, Buttercup. I'm sorry.
Gosh, have you ever seen blackout Andy? You look just like him.
No, I'm gonna see you. Yeah, not at all. Look at my profile picture. That's what I always pretty
look like. And nobody's talking about you. You crazy old lady. Who are you talking to?
You don't know maybe any one of the other four people on stream here three
Well, I don't know you're talking to so anyway. I answered your question about why I love animals so much
So what's your story?
What's my story my story is that I like animals to what are you talking about I need to have a sanctuary
Yes
Why don't you be why don't you be honest with the lady and tell her how much of a troll you are Brad?
Just tell her you're a known old troll old lady knows exactly how much of a troll I am
Yeah
That's one thing I'm grateful about that's why this guy you know
This guy's very disrespectful. This guy's a very disrespectful
Yeah
If I'm so disrespectful, why don't you let myself show myself for who I am?
If I am this way, why don't you let me show myself for who I am?
Anyway, psyche
Yeah, so I answered the question and he won't tell us his story. What why what's he doesn't have it?
He knows signal 66
Signal 66 does not have a story besides being a troll the way
She's just a fucking troll, bro
We're back here's your chat cheers
Animals over humans, okay, that's the truth. Yo cash. Do you drink or you're just like sober?
No, I don't
You don't drink at all
Fuck
How old are you?
She doesn't have to tell you her age. Why are you asking her for her age?
I didn't ask you know you asked her you're asking can I didn't ask you I didn't ask you
She feels uncomfortable. You're asking her personal questions
Could you give me your social security number and date of birth?
No, you cannot give that signal in the bulb and though
Oh my goodness grace some people do though then somebody just flashes ID yeah
Okay, I have a short clip here's a short clip
This is why Sam and doesn't cam up and he also fights with elbow in this clip. Let's have a look
There's a short clip here. We go Sam and makes excuses for why you didn't came up and
Elbow calls Sam and out. Okay. Here we go. That's that looks good. You see it on the screen yet. Yep
Oh my gosh this language on it. Okay terrible. Okay here we go.
That fucking table my nigga and then this nigga fucking
Here we go here we go with the noise
Like he's
You know I have people over right too.
It never looks like you're laughing.
Oh, but it's like you said you got all this money making it in.
Why you got a fucking picnic table?
He didn't lock the legs, right?
That's gotta be it.
He didn't lock the legs.
Just don't get it.
I got a juice story monitor.
Yeah, but a computer table on call. I think I got I got two monitor. I got I got like 10 sneakers and
The monitor in the fucking when I slam it like I'll be banging the table
And we're just bed bed bed in the middle or like fold it
And where I sit that is right in the middle. So I probably got height
I think when I got height and with the headset and weekend
So when I sometimes I go, that's why I don't want to come up.
Sometimes, you know, yeah, there's that little like, like that metal piece that you like,
like, pull to like lock it.
So like, over time, when you banging it, it like wiggles, you know, the metal thing.
And then it finally just gave.
Tripp he talk about how much money he has why I know bro like you can go get a desk from Ikea for mad chief
You don't even need to pay for premium just use an ad blocker it's free
Please turn this off
What do you want to hear from everyone here at the time?
What's that we want to do to get?
Hold on a second.
You be bragging about how much money you got, nigga,
and you got a fucking affordable table there.
It don't matter how ghetto you are, motherfucker.
Let me be, nigga.
You should see my table.
How much is lean nowadays?
Right. You should see my table before this. It was two crates and mom. I don't even
Milk crates
Bb live around the corner from you Bb bring this nigga computer table. I'll give you the money
And what's the problem on rumble? That's what I'm asking my nigga. I'm sure it's dude. He's the purpose is not me
He's saying it's his code. It's his code. Yeah
He's not fucking with the doxin so he doesn't want it on it
But check that's what elbow wants niggas to do
That's what I know see elders. I don't want to
I've been people but that's why I let that let that nigga be know what elbow elbow wants to be everybody
He wants to make everybody become like him.
I'm gonna never be like Elbow.
You did it.
Never.
I would dodge kids.
I would never look up kids.
I don't know if we do that shit.
Nigga.
I did dodge Barry, though.
You tried to dodge Barry.
Yeah, so Barry go live.
Tag up with Barry.
You tried to dodge Barry.
I never looked up kids.
I never looked up kids either.
Nigga never looked up kids.
Look, I said you looked up family members.
Yes.
Who family members did I look up?
Kate.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank
Okay. That's enough of that. Okay. I mean, wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Okay. Slugger, Sam, I, I promise you're reading home. Stay. I'll let you in a minute, but I'm going to, I'm going to get a few more cards for Slugger. Okay. Slugger, you also got this car. He says butterflies. Whenever you see a butterfly, float her through the grass.
It's to remind you of the love of those who have passed and so maybe there's a message from a past on love one
They'll get some kind of animal omen. It could be a butterfly. It could be it could be something else
But maybe there is possibly some messages from the other side for you
There's also sleep and maybe you're gonna see in a dream. It says underneath the nighttime skies fairies seeing you lullabies
Okay, okay got that one and then I'll get one more deck
And this one's the C melodies, this one says move, barnacles only grow on a docked ship, okay?
Maybe time to move around.
This one says perseverance, and it says stay the course,
and so whatever direction you're going on something is the right direction,
so continue staying the course with that, and...
We also have choose wisely says be discerning. You don't have to keep everything in your net
Okay, and so maybe a choice choice about something to make. Okay. We have sick coming back. Hope you like that. Is this the short?
Yeah, yeah, I do
Thank you
You like that you like that. Okay. Well the butterfly one it's funny because I was
There's an individual who means a lot to me and I and when I thought of them the other day it was
In a butterfly way an angelic butterfly
Hey, um, it is Sunday out to them. I'm smoking their pack right now
942 and it's not blocking speed. Well, Nancy got out to them. You said they're all dead now. Shout out to them
I'm smoking their pack. Okay. Well, you know, like love to everybody. Hey, I'm gonna wrap up
I mean love love to love to your homies. They ain't a prick right now
You guys I hope you hey say I hope you have a beautiful day
I hope you have a beautifully slugger Sam. Thank you everyone. That was on the show today
We had a nice nice full full chat and panel and it was fun some interesting characters as usual
Everyone have a great day. I'll be back this afternoon. Okay, and I'll be on have you could only shut up for a fucking
Yeah, you as well. Thank you. Hey sake you take care of yourself. Okay. Love you guys
Have a good day guys. Hey, hey psyche. Maybe we don't kill yourself next time. All right. I won't I won't thanks so much
Thank you so much. Okay. I'm gonna play a video on the way out and enjoy guys
Okay, have a great day and I love you. Okay
Here here's like a little
Welcome to the Cult of Psyche!
Please take a lantern. Sanitize your mirror and remember...
This is not a real cult.
Our dental plan is terrible!
This guy is the war of existential fear.
Terrors have seen things.
The open panel starts at 9x905
We've left space-time
A wizard argues young with Chad
A cryptid's microphone sounds bad
A troll rides to just debate
The new interrupts for 48 consecutive minutes
What a feat!
The shadow volume says hit delete
Someone cries the earth is flat
Someone else has proved the cat
The cat declaims to take a side
Discernment means it went outside
Come to the cult
Wrapping on the stream
You're cleaning
The ectoplasm machine
The military replied, I need more proof
Wonder yelled a glowing sphere discernment said that's Paul's chandelier
Transformation grew new-ing
The library has every text
But nobody knows which book is next
The rituals are strictly voluntary
Except returning books to the library
To guard your freedom, mind and growth
The intro music absolutely slaps, so sing
The gate re-handle remains chaotic
And your application to become Supreme Assistant Deputy
Junior Lantern, Barrier is still under review
Bring one small secret underneath my tiny hat
And a chili's where the enchanted freeway ends
With the bird-certificating glitter runes
Hey, with the PM our friendship's through
What did that punctuation do?
The LaCroix hit the floor
Our emotional support possum
Said I can
Says he's our treasurer
But everybody knows the truth
He's an ageless forest oracle in business casual youth
During rituals he hazes one immortal hand and says
Circle back next quarter to the existential dread
The brunch incident, we signed the napkin, we took the oath, bring forth thinking, crystal
of vibes, it author, he did, sing him to live, one chicken by the whole grace, if the maw
you're worth.